使用称为磁力计的传感器测量磁场。
Magnetic field is measured using a sensor called a magnetometer.
最常见的固态磁力计类型是霍尔效应传感器，它可以测量
The most common type of solid state magnetometer is a Hall effect sensor and it measures the
磁场垂直于芯片表面。
magnetic field normal to the chip surface.
能够测量磁场的三个正交分量是非常有用的
It’s very useful to be able to measure the three orthogonal components of magnetic field
向量。
vector.
因此，通常，三个正交霍尔效应传感器被封装到单个芯片中
So typically, three orthogonal Hall effect sensors are packaged in to a single chip along
与所有相关的电子设备，通常这些都有一个简单的串行接口
with all the associated electronics and typically these have a simple serial interface that
允许它们轻松连接到微控制器。
allows them to be easily connected to a micro-controller.
因此，为了确定身体在空间中的方向，我们使用加速度计
So, in order to determine the orientation of a body in space, we use the accelerometers
确定向下方向，重力矢量的方向。
to determine the downward direction, the direction of the gravity vector.
并且，我们用它来确定水平面中的磁场分量
And, we use that to determine the magnetic field component in the horizontal plane which
我们可以认为它与传统机械上的针尖方向相同
we can think of as being the same as the direction of the needle points on a traditional mechanical
罗盘。
compass.
为了使这个有形，再次考虑我的手机的例子，我附上了一个
To make this tangible, consider again the example of my phone and I have attached a
身体框架到手机。
body frame to the phone.
z轴在屏幕之外，y轴在屏幕上方，x轴在屏幕上方
The z-axis is out of the screen, y-axis is up the screen and the x-axis is across the
屏幕从左到右。
screen from left to right.
我要将磁力计与每个轴对齐，结果称为三轴
I’m going to align a magnetometer with each of these axes and the result is called a tri-axial
磁力计，因为那里有三个磁力计。
magnetometer because there are three magnetometers there.
现在让我们谈谈我们如何处理磁力计的信息。
Let’s talk now about how we process the information from the magnetometer.
再一次，我有一个世界坐标系，表示为零。
Once again, I have a world coordinate frame denoted zero.
再次，z轴平行于重力矢量。
Once again, the z-axis is parallel to the gravity vector.
它直指向上。
It’s pointing straight upwards.
并且，x轴与磁北对齐。
And, the x-axis is aligned with the magnetic north.
在这种情况下，我可以根据世界参考编写磁场矢量
In this case, I can write the magnetic field vector with respect to the world reference
坐标框架为B，我可以查看的磁场矢量的大小
coordinate frame as B, the magnitude of the magnetic field vector which I can look up
如果我知道我在这个星球上的位置，以及磁倾角的余弦和正弦，就在桌子上
in a table if I know my location on the planet, and the cosine and sine of the magnetic inclination
角度。
angle.
该向量位于xz平面中。
This vector lies in the x-z plane.
它在y方向上没有任何组件。
It has got no component in the y direction.
从世界框架到车身框架的旋转变换是根据世界框架给出的
The rotational transform from the world frame to the body frame is given in terms of the
滚动，俯仰和偏航角度。
roll, pitch and yaw angles.
我们已经讨论过如何从加速度计确定滚转角和俯仰角
We have already talked about how to determine the roll and pitch angles from the accelerometer
测量。
measurements.
手机中的磁力计测量坐标系B和中的磁场
The magnetometers in the phone measure the magnetic field in the coordinate frame B and
这让我可以写下这段关系。
that allows me to write this relationship.
而且，现在我们可以求出偏航角psi，它就是滚转角和俯仰角
And, now we can solve for the yaw angle psi and it is in terms of the roll and pitch angles
我们根据加速度计测量结果确定。
that we determined from the accelerometer measurements.
测得的磁场强度BX，BY和BZ，已知的磁场长度
The measured magnetic field strength, BX, BY and BZ, the known length of the magnetic
场矢量，大写B和已知的倾角，大写I.
field vector, capital B, and the known inclination angle, capital I.
如果我们知道我们在地球表面的位置，我们可以查看B和I。
And both B and I, we can look up if we know our location on the surface of the planet.
地球的磁场很弱。
The magnetic field of the earth is quite weak.
因此，磁力计需要对磁场非常敏感，这就是磁力计
Therefore, magnetometers need to be very sensitive to magnetic field and this makes magnetometers
非常容易受到电流流动产生的杂散磁场的影响
very susceptible to stray magnetic fields that are created by electric currents flowing
内部电子设备和电动机。
inside electronic devices and also from electric motors.
建造在室内操作的机器人的机器人专家经常受到结构的挫败
Roboticists building robots that operate indoors are often frustrated by the structural
建筑物中扭曲地球磁场的钢构件。
steel elements of the building which distort the earth’s magnetic field.
墙上还有电源线，还有Wi-Fi接入点和设备
There are also power cables in the walls and there are Wi-Fi access points and equipment
壁橱也会产生磁场，这可能会混淆主要依赖的机器人
closets which also create magnetic field which can confuse robots that rely predominantly
关于磁场传感。
on magnetic field sensing.
我真的很喜欢探索远方的先锋十号卫星的旧照片
I really like this old picture of the Pioneer ten satellite which is exploring the far reaches
我们的太阳系。背面有一堆电子设备和火箭发动机
of our solar system. There’s a bunch of electronics and a rocket motor on the back
一个大盘子，指向地球的行星。
of a large dish which is pointed back at Planet Earth.
并且，在长长的细长臂上是磁力计仪器，它感应到局部磁场
And, on a long slender boom is the magnetometer instrument which is sensing the local magnetic
他们可以从其他电子产品中找到远离它们的位置
field and they’ve position that is far away as they can from the rest of the electronics
在航天器上。
in the space craft.
而且，正是由于这个原因，磁力计对杂散磁场非常敏感
And, that’s for exactly this reason that magnetometer is very sensitive to stray magnetic
领域。
fields.